<resources>
    <string name="app_name">OrderFoodOL</string>
    <string name="login_text">Login</string>
    <string name="login_btn_text">GO！</string>
    <string name="login_username_hint">Please enter your username or mobile phone number</string>
    <string name="login_password_hint">Please enter your password</string>
    <string name="signup_username_hint">Please enter your username</string>
    <string name="signup_phoneNumber_hint" >Please input your mobile phone number (China)</string>
    <string name="signup_text" >注册</string>
    <string name="login_signup" >Don\'t have an account?</string>
    <string name="buttomAdd">add one to cart</string>
    <string name="buttonSub" >sub one from cart</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment" >Helloblankfragment</string>
    <string name="pay_title" >Please enter the payment code</string>
    <string name="defaultValue">default</string>

    <!--    商品信息    -->
    <string name="dish_1" >The big MAC</string>
    <string name="dish_2" >Plain pearl milk tea</string>
    <string name="dish_3" >Bacon and egg croissants with cheese</string>
    <string name="dish_4" >Coca-Cola</string>
    <string name="dish_5" >Double cheeseburger</string>
    <string name="dish_6" >McMuffin burger bucket</string>
    <string name="dish_7" >Braised chicken leg McMuffin with double Original Flavor</string>
    <string name="dish_8" >Coca-Cola Zero</string>
    <string name="dish_9" >Green pepper flavor half chicken</string>
    <string name="dish_10" >Popular fort fort bucket</string>
    <string name="dish_11" >Four sets of snack buckets</string>
    <string name="dish_12" >Double Angus MAX thick beef Bacon Fort</string>
    <string name="dish_13" >Tablet support</string>
    <string name="dish_14" >Pork tenderloin wheat full marks</string>
    <string name="dish_15" >Corn cup</string>
    <string name="dish_16" >Apple slices</string>
    <string name="dish_17" >Chocolate novelty</string>
    <string name="dish_18" >Grilled chicken tropicana</string>
    <string name="dish_19" >Preserved egg and chicken congee</string>
    <string name="dish_20" >Spicy chicken wings</string>
    <string name="dish_21" >Superior soya-bean milk</string>
    <string name="dish_22" >Bacon croissant with cheese</string>
    <string name="dish_23" >Ceylon tea</string>
    <string name="dish_24" >The hamburger</string>
    <string name="dish_25" >That\'s a big chicken chop</string>
    <string name="dish_26" >Bucket of fried chicken</string>
    <string name="dish_27" >Cheeseburger</string>
    <string name="dish_28" >Minute Maid 100% apple juice</string>
    <string name="dish_29" >Original Braised chicken leg McMuffin</string>
    <string name="dish_30" >Stir-fried double egg burger with German Thuringian sausage</string>
    <string name="dish_31" >Angus MAX Thick cow Bacon Fort</string>
    <string name="dish_32" >Mai Mai Chicken bucket</string>
    <string name="dish_33" >The hamburger</string>
    <string name="dish_34" >Fish steak Burger for kids</string>
    <string name="dish_35" >Double deep sea cod fort</string>
    <string name="dish_36" >Stay on the chicken</string>
    <string name="dish_37" >Enjoy a full morning meal</string>
    <string name="dish_38" >Strawberry new land</string>
    <string name="dish_39" >Cheese and egg McMuffins</string>
    <string name="dish_40" >Corn cup (small)</string>
    <string name="dish_41" >Chicken McNuggets (5 pieces)</string>
    <string name="dish_42" >Chicken McNuggets (4 pieces)</string>
    <string name="dish_43" >It\'s a double cow fort</string>
    <string name="dish_44" >Superior soya-bean milk</string>
    <string name="dish_45" >Minute Maid Sunshine Orange</string>
    <string name="dish_46" >Fresh pancetta for a full morning meal</string>
    <string name="dish_47" >0 proof bubble beer</string>
    <string name="dish_48" >fillet-o-fish</string>
    <string name="dish_49" >Cheese fried double egg burger</string>
    <string name="dish_50" >Angus MAX Thick beef cheeseburger</string>
    <string name="dish_51" >Lemon tea flavored drink</string>
    <string name="dish_52" >Mai Mai Crisp Sauce Chicken (Top leg steak)</string>
    <string name="dish_53" >There are bellagio</string>
    <string name="dish_54" >Porridge with crispy bamboo shoot and chicken with snow vegetables</string>
    <string name="dish_55" >Large Crispy chicken steak McMuffin</string>
    <string name="dish_56" >McSwirl Oreo Original</string>
    <string name="dish_57" >Bacon and veggie Double beef burger</string>
    <string name="dish_58" >Chicken with McMuffin Sauce (chicken breast)</string>
    <string name="dish_59" >Coconut water</string>
    <string name="dish_60" >Apple slices</string>
    <string name="dish_61" >Braised chicken leg sausage for a full morning meal</string>
    <string name="dish_62" >McSpicy Chicken Leg burger</string>
    <string name="dish_63" >Ham steak with wheat full marks</string>
    <string name="dish_64" >Fresh coffee</string>
    <string name="dish_65" >Ice cream cone</string>
    <string name="dish_66" >Pure milk (UHT)</string>
    <string name="dish_67" >Three sets of small food box</string>
    <string name="dish_68" >Pure milk (UHT)</string>
    <string name="dish_69" >wedges</string>
    <string name="dish_70" >Ham steak and egg croissant</string>
    <string name="dish_71" >Pancetta and egg McMuffin</string>
    <string name="dish_72" >Not a chicken</string>
    <string name="dish_73" >French Fries (mini)</string>
    <string name="dish_74" >Double Angus MAX Thick cheeseburger</string>
    <string name="dish_75" >McTornado ™ Oreo Strawberry Flavor</string>
    <string name="dish_76" >Chicken with Mai Mai Crisp Sauce (Pipa leg)</string>
    <string name="dish_77" >Original braised chicken drumstick burger</string>
    <string name="dish_78" >Brittle article balm</string>
    <string name="dish_79" >Minute Maid 100% Apple Juice (small)</string>
    <string name="dish_80" >Pork and egg McMuffin</string>
    <string name="dish_81" >German Turingen sausage</string>
    <string name="dish_82" >Pineapple pie</string>
    <string name="dish_83" >Ice dew packaging drinking water</string>
    <string name="dish_84" >Sprite</string>
    <string name="dish_85" >Energy eggs</string>
    <string name="dish_86" >Hot chocolate</string>
    <string name="dish_87" >Thuringian sausage Good morning nutrition roll</string>
    <string name="dish_88" >Taro pie</string>
    <string name="dish_89" >What a great set meal</string>
    <string name="dish_90" >Ice dew packaging drinking water</string>
    <string name="dish_91" >French Classics</string>
    <string name="dish_92" >French fries</string>
    <string name="dish_93" >Stir fried Pork Fillet with Double Egg Burger</string>
    <string name="dish_94" >Crispy Potato Cake</string>
    <string name="dish_95" >Ham Steak Morning Roll</string>
    <!--详情信息-->
    <string name="desc_1" >A classic choice for 50 years! Two pieces of 100% pure beef cakes, together with soft bread sprinkled with fresh sesame, fresh and refreshing lettuce, onions and pickles, supplemented by smooth cheese and delicious sauce, are layered with rich ingredients to create an ultimate delicious experience.</string>
    <string name="desc_2" >Silky milk tea with soft waxy pearls, cold and hot by people.</string>
    <string name="desc_3" >The puffy and soft Kesong, together with tender bacon, soft eggs and rich cheese, is full of vitality all day long.</string>
    <string name="desc_4" >It\'s very exciting to match with dinner snacks!</string>
    <string name="desc_5" >100% pure beef is integrated with double layer soft cheese, which is paired with soft bread and delicious sauce. It has twice the taste temptation, and no one can stop it!</string>
    <string name="desc_6" >McMuffin burger bucket</string>
    <string name="desc_7" >Chicken leg meat, I want double! The double-layer boneless chicken leg is tender, smooth and juicy. During the frying process, 0 oil is added. It is supplemented by fresh crisp lettuce shreds and spicy braised chicken sauce. It tastes rich and tastes better.</string>
    <string name="desc_8" >Sugar free, smooth and wonderful!</string>
    <string name="desc_9" >The chicken skin is golden and crisp, and the chicken is soft, tender and juicy. The flavor is diversified, full and three-dimensional. With the exclusive freshness locking technology, every mouthful is fresh and delicious, and the meaning is still endless.</string>
    <string name="desc_10" >Popular fort fort bucket</string>
    <string name="desc_11" >Four sets of snack buckets</string>
    <string name="desc_12" >Select two pieces of 100% Angus beef pie, with bacon, yellow cheddar cheese slice and fresh Roman lettuce. The unique hot melting process allows the cheese to melt slowly, and the silk permeates into the beef fiber - the oil of semi melted cheese and meat pie blend with each other, making the taste more rich and fragrant!</string>
    <string name="desc_13" >1 taro pie+1 bag of apple slices+1 cup of Meiyuyuan Sunshine Orange (small cup)</string>
    <string name="desc_14" >Fresh, tender and juicy pork fillet, baked muffin, with a little salty cheese, layer upon layer, the taste is slightly crisp, the interior is soft, and the taste is endless!</string>
    <string name="desc_15" >The grains are full and juicy. Fragrance! Sweet! Cool!</string>
    <string name="desc_16" >Shandong Red Fuji is preferred. It is fresh, refreshing, sour and sweet. It is a nutritious meal for children.</string>
    <string name="desc_17" >The mellow and delicate ice cream, together with the mellow and silky chocolate sauce, is intoxicated with the mellow and silky fragrance.</string>
    <string name="desc_18" >1 original braised chicken leg burger+1 bag of apple slices+1 cup of zero coke (medium)</string>
    <string name="desc_19" >Selected Northeast rice, with a star rice ratio of 12:1, and carefully boiled for 95 minutes until the grains bloom. The thick, soft and glutinous porridge base is made of selected Songhua eggs and healthy chicken. It tastes rich and warms the heart and stomach.</string>
    <string name="desc_20" >The selected high-quality white feather chicken wings are hot and tasty, which can stimulate the taste.</string>
    <string name="desc_21" >Traditional Chinese drinks are only available during breakfast.</string>
    <string name="desc_22" >The elaborately roasted Kesong, together with smoked bacon and high-quality cheese slices, is crisp and delicious, and salty.</string>
    <string name="desc_23" >The fragrant hot black tea will keep you awake all day long</string>
    <string name="desc_24" >100% pure beef! Seasoned with a little salt and pepper, served with crisp pickles and onions, and added with delicious tomato sauce to create a classic taste.</string>
    <string name="desc_25" >The strong and hot pepper, the pungent garlic and onion, and the hot black pepper combine to form a unique flavor.</string>
    <string name="desc_26" >Bucket of fried chicken</string>
    <string name="desc_27" >100% pure beef is integrated with soft and fragrant cheese, with crispy pickles and onion granules, supplemented by delicious sauce. It has a rich taste and can emerge immediately after being bitten!</string>
    <string name="desc_28" >100% apple juice in carton.</string>
    <string name="desc_29" >The original boneless chicken steaks are tender, smooth and juicy. During the frying process, 0 oil is added, supplemented by fresh crispy lettuce shreds and fragrant braised chicken sauce. They taste rich and better.</string>
    <string name="desc_30" >Two high-quality eggs, with original taste and German style Thuringian sausage, have a richer taste.</string>
    <string name="desc_31" >Selected 100% Angus beef pie, with bacon, yellow cheddar cheese slice and fresh Roman lettuce, the unique hot melting process allows the cheese to melt slowly, and the silk permeates into the beef fiber - the oil of semi melted cheese and meat pie blend together, making the taste more rich and fragrant!</string>
    <string name="desc_32" >Mai Mai Chicken bucket</string>
    <string name="desc_33" >100% pure beef! Seasoned with a little salt and pepper, served with crisp pickles and onions, and added with delicious tomato sauce to create a classic taste.</string>
    <string name="desc_34" >Cod cake made from deep-sea cod, paired with fresh tomatoes, has a unique, balanced and delicious flavor.</string>
    <string name="desc_35" >Two pieces of deep-sea cod fish cake are specially selected. The meat is white and delicate, rich in high-quality protein. One bite of them will leave a fragrance, which will double the satisfaction. I want both delicious food and nutrition! (Mainly supplied by restaurants)</string>
    <string name="desc_36" >Crisp and refreshing lettuce, giving you plant fiber; The golden crispy chicken comes from the carefully cultivated high-quality tender chicken. With nutrition, you can have a healthy choice with good taste.</string>
    <string name="desc_37" >The delicate whole meal featured tender and juicy pork fillets, slightly salty and juicy. Fried eggs are golden and soft, with a smooth taste; The muffin is evenly baked with a slightly crisp surface; Potato cake is golden and crisp, with soft inside. Select high-quality fresh brewed coffee with wheat coffee, and start with breakfast today!</string>
    <string name="desc_38" >The mellow and delicate ice cream is matched with fresh and delicious strawberry jam to meet sweet memories.</string>
    <string name="desc_39" >The round steamed egg tastes smooth, and the baked muffin tastes slightly crispy. It is layered with the salty cheese to open a full day!</string>
    <string name="desc_40" >The grains are full and juicy. Fragrance! Sweet! Cool!</string>
    <string name="desc_41" >Strictly select high-quality chicken, precisely control the temperature, and lock the gravy and flavor. The skin is golden and crisp, and the chicken is tender, smooth and juicy. With the special dip sauce, the taste is unforgettable.</string>
    <string name="desc_42" >Strictly select high-quality chicken, precisely control the temperature, and lock the gravy and flavor. The skin is golden and crisp, and the chicken is tender, smooth and juicy. With the special dip sauce, the taste is unforgettable.</string>
    <string name="desc_43" >Two 100% beef patties are specially selected. They are seasoned with a little salt and pepper and paired with German Thuringian sausages. They are very fleshy and delicious!</string>
    <string name="desc_44" >Traditional Chinese drinks are only available during breakfast.</string>
    <string name="desc_45" >Vitamin+fiber, nutrition should be fresh.</string>
    <string name="desc_46" >Delicate selection of ham for the whole meal, fried eggs are golden and soft, with a smooth taste; The muffin is evenly baked with a slightly crisp surface; Potato cake is golden and crisp, with soft inside. Select high-quality fresh brewed coffee with wheat coffee, and start with breakfast today!</string>
    <string name="desc_47" >The air bubbles are full of momentum, and the light beer fragrance makes you refreshing.</string>
    <string name="desc_48" >The cod cake is made of deep sea cod. Its outer skin is golden and crisp, and its inner side is fresh and juicy. Delicious fish with delicious salad sauce has a unique flavor.</string>
    <string name="desc_49" >Two high-quality eggs, original flavor, stir fry soft taste, more balanced nutrition with cheese!</string>
    <string name="desc_50" >100% Angus beef cake is selected, matched with secret cheese flavor sauce and fresh tomato slices. The unique hot melting process allows the cheese to melt slowly, and the silk permeates into the beef fiber - the oil of semi melted cheese and meat cake blends with each other, making the taste more rich and fragrant!</string>
    <string name="desc_51" >Sweet taste, fresh and moist.</string>
    <string name="desc_52" >Innovative black technology makes American style fried chicken. The skin is fragrant and crisp, and the inside is fresh and juicy. Every mouthful tastes delicious, and every piece is big!</string>
    <string name="desc_53" >1 cheeseburger+1 pair of spicy chicken wings+1 cup of zero temperature coke (medium)</string>
    <string name="desc_54" >Selected Northeast rice, with a star rice ratio of 12:1, and carefully boiled for 95 minutes until the grains bloom. The thick, soft and glutinous porridge is very good. It can be served with tender chicken and delicious shredded bamboo shoots. It is smooth and refreshing, warm and warm.</string>
    <string name="desc_55" >The golden brown wheat flavored chicken nuggets are slightly crisp on the surface, with a special smell of black pepper. The muffins are crisp, soft, hot and fresh inside!</string>
    <string name="desc_56" >The smoothness of ice cream and the crispness of Oreo biscuits blend together, creating a wonderful black and white combination to create an infinite new taste.</string>
    <string name="desc_57" >One layer of crispy lettuce, one slice of fresh tomato, two slices of bacon, two slices of beef, and one layer of special sauce! It\'s so satisfying to bite!</string>
    <string name="desc_58" >Innovative black technology makes American style fried chicken. The skin is fragrant and crisp, and the inside is fresh and juicy. Every mouthful tastes delicious, and every piece is big!</string>
    <string name="desc_59" >Refreshing and pleasant, it is an option for reducing fat.</string>
    <string name="desc_60" >Shandong Red Fuji is preferred. It is fresh, refreshing, sour and sweet. It is a nutritious meal for children.</string>
    <string name="desc_61" >The delicate whole meal featured fresh, tender and juicy chicken leg with mild black pepper flavor. Fried eggs are golden and soft, with a smooth taste; The muffin is evenly baked with a slightly crisp surface; Potato cake is golden and crisp, with soft inside; Sausages are fresh, tender and juicy. With the selected high-quality fresh brewed coffee of wheat coffee, you can start from breakfast today!</string>
    <string name="desc_62" >The leading product specially developed for the \"Chinese Stomach\" is the tender and juicy chicken leg under the golden, crisp and hot appearance, coupled with the fresh lettuce and delicious salad sauce, which will leave you with endless aftertaste and impress your picky taste buds.</string>
    <string name="desc_63" >The ham grilled meat pie is soft and juicy, with a Q - shaped texture, and is served with fresh and crisp lettuce. Start with breakfast today!</string>
    <string name="desc_64" >With high-quality coffee powder, a beautiful day begins with attractive coffee fragrance.</string>
    <string name="desc_65" >The mellow and delicate ice cream is paired with the crispy cylinder to bite off the sweetness and crispness!</string>
    <string name="desc_66" >Drink milk, grow tall.</string>
    <string name="desc_67" >Assemble many classic snacks, one box will give you super satisfaction!</string>
    <string name="desc_68" >Drink milk, grow tall.</string>
    <string name="desc_69" >Delicately cut Victory V shape, the mouth is crisp and salty, the original smell of potatoes is matched with a light black pepper flavor, and you can\'t stop!</string>
    <string name="desc_70" >Kesong tastes soft and puffy, with fresh and tender egg skin and juicy ham steak. Tasty and delicious.</string>
    <string name="desc_71" >The upper layer is lightly smoked and roasted fragrant fried bacon, and the lower layer is round steamed egg with smooth taste. It is paired with slightly crispy baked muffins and brackish cheese, which are complete in color, aroma and taste.</string>
    <string name="desc_72" >1 pair of Spicy Chicken Wings+5 pieces of Merlot Chicken+1 cup of Zero Coke (medium)</string>
    <string name="desc_73" >The mini French fries tailored for Happy Paradise meal are selected from high-quality potatoes. The surface is slightly crispy, the inside is soft, and the taste is delicious with a little salt!</string>
    <string name="desc_74" >Two pieces of 100% Angus beef cakes are selected, matched with the special cheese flavored sauce and fresh tomato slices. The unique hot melting process allows the cheese to melt slowly, and the threads penetrate into the beef fiber - the fat of the semi melted cheese and the meat cake blend with each other, making the taste more rich and fragrant!</string>
    <string name="desc_75" >The creamy ice cream is integrated with the crispy Oreo biscuits, and a little strawberry jam is added to mix with different fresh flavors.</string>
    <string name="desc_76" >Innovative black technology makes American style fried chicken. The skin is fragrant and crisp, and the inside is fresh and juicy. Every mouthful tastes delicious, and every piece is big!</string>
    <string name="desc_77" >0 oil, high protein, favorite for fitness and fat reducing people! The original boneless chicken chops are tender, smooth and juicy. They are seasoned with onions and pepper, accompanied by fresh green lettuce and spicy braised chicken sauce, which will definitely make your fingers move!</string>
    <string name="desc_78" >The surface is golden, and the taste is puffy and crisp.</string>
    <string name="desc_79" >100% apple juice in carton.</string>
    <string name="desc_80" >The fresh, tender and juicy pork fillet, together with the smooth steamed egg, the slightly crisp baked muffin, and the salty cheese, is layered, nutritious and delicious.</string>
    <string name="desc_81" >It is fresh, tender and juicy. It has a strong fried and roasted taste, with a mild spice taste.</string>
    <string name="desc_82" >The soft sandwich, the crisp shell, a bite, it is really happy to explode!</string>
    <string name="desc_83" >Drink more water to promote metabolism.</string>
    <string name="desc_84" >It\'s refreshing to match with dinner snacks!</string>
    <string name="desc_85" >Round steamed egg tastes smooth and brings full positive energy!</string>
    <string name="desc_86" >It is mellow, fragrant and smooth, and can\'t put it down.</string>
    <string name="desc_87" >The crust is thin and moderate, soft and chewy. Stir fried egg, rich cheese, fresh and tender Thuringian sausage, and classic mustard flavor sauce, with rich taste. Take it from breakfast today!</string>
    <string name="desc_88" >The soft sandwich, the crisp shell, a bite, it is really happy to explode!</string>
    <string name="desc_89" >1 double-layer beef burger with bacon and vegetable crisps+1 bag of apple slices+1 cup of coke (medium)</string>
    <string name="desc_90" >Drink more water to promote metabolism.</string>
    <string name="desc_91" >The palate is soft and crisp, with milk fragrance and rich butter fragrance.</string>
    <string name="desc_92" >Selected high-quality potatoes, slightly crispy on the surface, soft inside, seasoned with a little salt, delicious!</string>
    <string name="desc_93" >Have two eggs for breakfast. Be better to yourself! Two authentic high-quality eggs are paired with pork fillet, which has a richer taste.</string>
    <string name="desc_94" >The outside is crisp, the inside is soft, and the inlet is slightly salty.</string>
    <string name="desc_95" >The crust is thin and moderate, soft and chewy. Stir fried egg, rich cheese, fresh and tender ham steak, with classic tomato sauce, rich taste. Take it from breakfast today!</string>
    <!--分类信息-->
    <string name="cate_1" >hamburger</string>
    <string name="cate_2" >drink</string>
    <string name="cate_3" >breakfast</string>
    <string name="cate_4" >Dessert</string>
    <string name="cate_5" >snack</string>
    <string name="cate_6" >happy meal </string>
    <string name="cate_7" >500 large card package</string>


    <string name="price_1" >17</string>
    <string name="price_2" >5</string>
    <string name="price_3" >8</string>
    <string name="price_4" >7</string>
    <string name="price_5" >16</string>
    <string name="price_6" >14</string>
    <string name="price_7" >10</string>
    <string name="price_8" >9</string>
    <string name="price_9" >13</string>
    <string name="price_10" >13</string>
    <string name="price_11" >14</string>
    <string name="price_12" >19</string>
    <string name="price_13" >30</string>
    <string name="price_14" >12</string>
    <string name="price_15" >8</string>
    <string name="price_16" >13</string>
    <string name="price_17" >25</string>
    <string name="price_18" >24</string>
    <string name="price_19" >9</string>
    <string name="price_20" >10</string>
    <string name="price_21" >11</string>
    <string name="price_22" >6</string>
    <string name="price_23" >8</string>
    <string name="price_24" >8</string>
    <string name="price_25" >10</string>
    <string name="price_26" >10</string>
    <string name="price_27" >20</string>
    <string name="price_28" >10</string>
    <string name="price_29" >7</string>
    <string name="price_30" >5</string>
    <string name="price_31" >17</string>
    <string name="price_32" >11</string>
    <string name="price_33" >8</string>
    <string name="price_34" >11</string>
    <string name="price_35" >18</string>
    <string name="price_36" >19</string>
    <string name="price_37" >12</string>
    <string name="price_38" >21</string>
    <string name="price_39" >12</string>
    <string name="price_40" >9</string>
    <string name="price_41" >15</string>
    <string name="price_42" >6</string>
    <string name="price_43" >19</string>
    <string name="price_44" >11</string>
    <string name="price_45" >6</string>
    <string name="price_46" >9</string>
    <string name="price_47" >11</string>
    <string name="price_48" >16</string>
    <string name="price_49" >10</string>
    <string name="price_50" >17</string>
    <string name="price_51" >7</string>
    <string name="price_52" >9</string>
    <string name="price_53" >28</string>
    <string name="price_54" >9</string>
    <string name="price_55" >9</string>
    <string name="price_56" >24</string>
    <string name="price_57" >20</string>
    <string name="price_58" >11</string>
    <string name="price_59" >8</string>
    <string name="price_60" >13</string>
    <string name="price_61" >8</string>
    <string name="price_62" >15</string>
    <string name="price_63" >6</string>
    <string name="price_64" >7</string>
    <string name="price_65" >26</string>
    <string name="price_66" >12</string>
    <string name="price_67" >9</string>
    <string name="price_68" >8</string>
    <string name="price_69" >15</string>
    <string name="price_70" >7</string>
    <string name="price_71" >5</string>
    <string name="price_72" >25</string>
    <string name="price_73" >11</string>
    <string name="price_74" >15</string>
    <string name="price_75" >27</string>
    <string name="price_76" >10</string>
    <string name="price_77" >16</string>
    <string name="price_78" >11</string>
    <string name="price_79" >8</string>
    <string name="price_80" >5</string>
    <string name="price_81" >6</string>
    <string name="price_82" >23</string>
    <string name="price_83" >11</string>
    <string name="price_84" >5</string>
    <string name="price_85" >5</string>
    <string name="price_86" >8</string>
    <string name="price_87" >8</string>
    <string name="price_88" >30</string>
    <string name="price_89" >24</string>
    <string name="price_90" >11</string>
    <string name="price_91" >10</string>
    <string name="price_92" >8</string>
    <string name="price_93" >10</string>
    <string name="price_94" >7</string>
    <string name="price_95" >11</string>
    <string-array name="setting_country">
        <item>China</item>
        <item>britain</item>
        <item>U.S.A</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="setting_language">
        <item>English</item>
        <item>Chinese</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="commit">payment</string>
    <string name="shopping_car_title">Shopping Cart</string>
    <string name="clear_shopping_car">empty</string>
    <string name="confirm_to_pay">confirm the payment</string>
    <string name="confirm_message">Are you sure you want to pay and generate an order\? \N Before paying, remember to open the shopping cart to see if there are any coupons~</string>
    <string name="confirm">confirm</string>
    <string name="cancel">cancel</string>

    <!--自定义口味-->
    <string name="spicyDegree">Spicy </string>
    <string name="spicy_1">Not spicy</string>
    <string name="spicy_2">Slightly spicy</string>
    <string name="spicy_3">Medium Spicy</string>
    <string name="spicy_4">Spicy</string>
    <string name="sweetDegree">Sweetness</string>
    <string name="sweet_1">0 points sweet</string>
    <string name="sweet_2">3 points sweet</string>
    <string name="sweet_3">7 points sweet</string>
    <string name="sweet_4">10 points sweet</string>
    <string name="shopping_car_wait_for_adding">There is no food in the shopping cart. Welcome guests to feed~</string>

    <!--    支付页面提示字段-->
    <string name="pay_sub_title">Pay to Lanyuan Canteen</string>
    <string name="pay_money">￥</string>
    <string name="pay_success">Payment succeeded</string>
    <string name="pay_fail">Payment failed, please check the payment password</string>
    <string name="pay_cancel">Payment cancellation</string>
    <string name="pay_set_title">Please set the payment password</string>
    <string name="pay_set_sub_title">The payment password cannot be modified. Please do not disclose the payment password to others</string>
    <!--    登录页面提示字段-->
    <string name="login_fail">Login failed, please check the account or password</string>
    <string name="login_username_empty">User name or mobile number cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="login_password_empty">Password cannot be empty</string>
    <!--    注册页面提示字段-->
    <string name="register_success">login was successful</string>
    <string name="register_fail">To set the payment password</string>
    <string name="register_username_empty">User name cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="register_password_empty">Password cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="register_password_less">Password is less than six digits</string>
    <string name="register_phone_empty">Mobile number cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="register_username_exist">User name already exists</string>
    <string name="register_phone_exist">Mobile number already exists</string>
    <string name="register_phone_error">Mobile number format error</string>
    <string name="chooseCoupon">Select coupon</string>
    <string name="coupon">coupon</string>
    <string name="history_orders">Historical Orders</string>
    <string name="recent_order">Recent Orders</string>
    <string name="Notification">notice</string>
    <string name="Nation">country</string>
    <string name="Language">language</string>
    <string name="Account">account</string>

    <string name="PEYOP">Please enter the old password</string>
    <string name="PEYNW">Please enter a new password</string>
    <string name="version">edition</string>
    <string name="update">to update</string>
    <string name="change">change</string>
    <string name="APPSETTING">APP settings</string>
    <string name="ONLINE">on-line</string>
    <string name="Hi">Hello</string>
    <string name="languagesetting">The language will be switched automatically according to your phone language</string>

</resources>